BRYAN K. DEMPS

[M] (508) 375-8873 [E] bdemps508@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Fund Administration manager and successful leader with experience across all Fund Administration disciplines. The following resume highlights a working knowledge of all functions within Fund Administration which include Financial Reporting, Fund Treasury, Compliance, Fund Performance, Tax Support and Legal Support. These skills are applied across multiple investment structures including: SEC Registered Mutual Funds, Offshore Trusts, Master Feeder and Hedge Fund of Funds. This foundation provides the expertise to solve Client issues, implement process improvement, facilitate stakeholder collaboration, thoughtful problem solving, focus and motivate team members resulting in issue resolution and high internal/external Client satisfaction in a time sensitive field which meets department, senior management and organization goals.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BROWN BROTHERS HARRIMAN & CO., Boston, MA, 2009 - Present

Financial Reporting Manager

Financial Reporting ("FR") manager with oversight responsibilities of offshore teams providing Fund Administration services to over 20 Institutional Clients based in Japan and Cayman via the Global Service Model:

- Managing and training FR Team providing annual accounts for Cayman structures in compliance with U.S. Generally Accepted Accounting Principles (U.S. GAAP), International Financial Reporting Standards (IFRS) and Liquidation basis of accounting standard.
- ➤ Audit oversight responsibility for over 100 Funds within defined deadlines.
- > Primary point of communication for all internal and external stakeholders concerning Fund audits (including auditors located in multiple time zones globally).
- > Evaluate U.S. GAAP and IFRS pronouncements to determine relevant application and presentation within financial statements.
- > Responsible for ensuring highest service levels for Institutional Clients in Japan/Europe and Cayman based Trustee's.
- > Collaborate across global time zones with internal production/system teams to incrementally improve financial statement quality and reduce production time.
- Establishing close relationships with internal departments globally enabling efficient resolution of FR and corporate problems cementing Client satisfaction with BBH Services.
- > Leading team that identifies and executes technology and operational solutions to Client/internal problems.
- > Oversight review and submission of Cayman regulatory filings. Review of Japanese regulatory filings.
- ➤ Assist Trustee's with ASC740 tax analysis.
- > Oversight of distribution calculations per Trustee/Unitholder authorization.
- > New Client on-boarding.

Bank of New York Mellon Corporation, Boston, MA., 2005 – 2008

Treasury Manager

Assistant Treasurer, Fund Officer and member of the security valuation committee reporting to the Vice-President and Chief Financial Officer with oversight responsibility of BNY Mellon service providers to Institutional Mutual Funds and Hedge Fund of Funds products.

- Treasury responsibilities included oversight of third-party custodian, administrator and accounting agent including review of third-party expense packages, budgeting, expense true-ups, line of credit use, security fair value pricing, distributions, capital and income allocation review and bill payment authorization.
- > Financial reporting oversight responsibilities included the coordination of the financial cycle with Legal, Auditors and third-party service providers.
- ➤ Final review of financial reports (Annual, Semi-Annual and Quarterly) ensuring compliance with U.S. GAAP reporting standards, N-1A and Rule S-X.
- > Other responsibilities include research of new regulatory disclosure requirements including coordination with counsel and auditors concerning implementation of regulations, participation in other ad-hoc projects as required.
- Oversight of SEC filings.

BRYAN K. DEMPS

[M] (508) 375-8873 [E] bdemps508@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (continued)

BROWN BROTHERS HARRIMAN & CO., Boston, MA., 1998 - 2005

Financial Reporting/Treasury Manager

Performed multiple mutual fund administration duties for onshore and offshore trusts which included: Financial Reporting (FR), Board book support and Assistant Treasury (AT).

- > Financial statement preparation in compliance with U.S. GAAP, N-1A, and Rule S-X.
- > Coordinate financial reporting audit with Client, Legal, Auditor, Printer and Fund Accounting.
- > Filed required schedules with the SEC including Form N-SAR, N-Q and Form N-CSR.
- > Interpretation of Trust Deed/Confidential Memorandum/Prospectus and internal fee schedules to determine expense budget setup and financial statement note disclosures.
- ➤ Work with Clients to establish AT operational workflow and initial/liquidation budget set-up.
- > Calculate distribution estimates and process Client approved distributions.
- ➤ Lead contact on FR/AT matters for Fund Management and overseas BBH offices-Tokyo, Hong Kong, London.
- > Establish and document FR and AT procedures to improve production methods and quality controls.
- > Recommended and implemented workflows to reach department and firm goals.
- > Fund budgeting and expense variance analysis and ensuring invoice payment.

STATE STREET CORPORATION, Quincy, MA., 1997 - 1998

Manager Fund Administration

Performed multiple mutual fund administration duties for SEC registered open-end funds which included Financial Reporting, Board book support and Assistant Treasury.

- > NAV oversight review including understanding drivers of NAV changes.
- > Coordinated financial reporting cycle including filing of required forms with the Securities and Exchange Commission.
- > Reviewed expense budgets including monitoring variances and suggesting updates to Clients.
- > Setup and reviewed NAV based total return calculations on the Fund Administration system.
- > Act as a primary contact for client questions and requests.
- Involved in ad-hoc projects and managed a support staff.

PNC/GIS FINANCIAL, Boston, MA., 1994 - 1997

Compliance Manager

Used knowledge of the Investment Company Act of 1940 and the Internal Revenue Code to review, monitor and process compliance reports for mutual funds and variable annuities.

- Monthly review, issue resolution and delivery to clients of over 200 compliance reports within defined time line.
- > Acted as primary contact for compliance issues for portfolio managers and external compliance officers.
- > Training and professional development of the compliance staff.
- Developed and implemented ad-hoc testing methods and procedures.
- > Supervised the continuing development of Excel models.
- Managed support staff.

SCUDDER, STEVENS AND CLARK, Boston, MA., 1992 - 1994

Fund Accountant

Oversight of custodian on matters concerning proprietary Institutional Money Funds:

- > Review of income calculation, average days to maturity, seven and thirty-day yields
- > Reconciliation of fund holdings
- Reviewed NAV based performance
- > Communicated daily with Custodian on topics involving Institutional Funds
- > Modified and improved models used to generate reports and analyze data in Microsoft Suite applications.

EDUCATION

Masters of Science in Financial Economics, Boston University, Boston, MA. Bachelor of Science in Business Administration, Northeastern University, Boston, MA COMPUTER EXPERIENCE: Microsoft Office: Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Access